站那兒別動
Stop right there.
把手放在我能看到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
脫襯衫
Shirt off!
快點
Come on!
褲子也脫了 快 狗娘養的
Pants off! Come on, motherfucker.
我一直以為我會在
I always thought my life would end like this,
某個鳥不生蛋的地方
in some Godforsaken place,
被一顆莫名而來的子彈了卻殘生
from a bullet I didn't see coming.
我只是從沒想過我會在乎
I just never thought I'd care.
《快槍查理》
"查理.斯威夫特 美國海軍陸戰隊光榮退役"
你應該不會願意看到
One thing you don't want to see,
大早上穿著正裝的我
me in a suit this early in the morning.
這代表著我正在工作
Means I'm working,
同時也意味著將會有人
which means someone is about
死於非命
to depart this life unexpectedly.
"密西西比州 比洛克希市"
-斯坦  -是我
-Stan.  -Yeah?
-他遲到了  -沒事的
-He's late.  -It's all right.
他會來的 OK?
He'll be there, okay?
嘿 聽著 我自己能搞定這傢伙
Hey, listen, I can do the guy myself.
-他現在就在那兒  -不不不
-He's there right now.  -No, no, no, no.
另外 我答應過鮑比.T 要給這孩子一個機會
Besides, I promised Bobby T we'd give this kid a shot.
他刀法不錯
Supposed to be pretty good with a knife.
是 你總這麼說 但…
Yeah, well that's what you keep saying, but..
好了 完事了給我打電話 OK?
Well, uh, call me when it's done, okay?
-他來了  -嘿 我給羅路買了這個
-He's here.  -Hey, I got these for Rollo.
我聽說他超愛吃甜甜圈
'Cause I.. I heard he's a donut junkie.
所以 我跟他說
So, I told him that he won
他在我們的每週抽獎中贏了一打甜甜圈
a dozen donuts at our weekly raffle.
他喜歡波士頓奶油
He loves Boston creams.
嗯… 為啥穿得這麼正式?
W.. What's with the suit?
-你這T恤又是咋回事?  - 哦 這是計劃的一部分
-What's with the shirt?  -Oh, it's part of the plan.
我自己做的(脆皮奶脆)
I made it myself.
-聰明吧?  -行
-That's pretty smart, right?  -Yeah.
不過那家店叫「酥皮奶酥"
Except Krispy Kremes are spelled with two K's.
誰他媽知道
Who the fuck knows that?
反正你不知道
Not you.
OK 動作快點 就一次機會
Okay, make it quick. You get one chance.
你搞砸的話 找他又得一頓好找
You fuck it up, he's in the wind again.
嘿
Hey.
別擔心 老傢伙
Don't worry, old timer.
我能搞定
I got this shit.
"根據維克托.吉士勒小說《槍猴》改編"
特雷弗
Trevor!
咋了?
Yeah?
這是什麼?
What is this?
好 夥計 好的 謝謝
All right, man. All right. Thanks.
再見
See ya!
-那就是羅路  -對
-That was Rollo.  -Yeah.
為什麼不用刀?
Why didn't you stab him?
我一直都用刀
That's what I always do.
-所以他們叫你刀仔  -沒錯
-Hence why they call you Blade.  -Yeah.
-我想換個花樣  -嗯哼?
-I thought I'd do something different.  -Mm  -hmm?
我想向斯坦展示我的其它技能和想像力
I wanna show Stan some range and imagination.
你做了什麼? 給他下毒?
What'd you do, poison him?
什麼鬼?
What the fuck?
波士頓奶油 寶貝
Boston cream, baby!
哇哦
Woo!
來
Come on.
你在甜甜圈裡放了什麼?
What did you put in the donut?
呃 那個 就像 一個小炸彈
Uh, just, like, a little blasting cap.
哦
Oh.
我是說 沒有頭
I mean, how's Beggar
拜加會認得沒有腦袋的羅路嗎?
gonna know it's Rollo without his head?
-呃 那可能就…  -你他媽給我閉嘴
-Well, there's like a..  -Shut the fuck up.
天哪
Sweet Jesus.
-班尼  -怎麼樣了?
-Benny.  -How'd it go?
那小伙兒給羅路餵了一個裝有炸彈的甜甜圈
Kid fed Rollo a donut with a bomb in it.
-聽起來挺酷的  -嗯哼
-That sounds kinda cool.  -Uh  -huh.
爆了他的頭
Blew his head off.
我是說 呃 斯坦聽到會尿褲子的
I mean.. Uh, Stan gonna shit himself.
嘿 聽著 沒必要打擾斯坦
Hey, listen, there's no need to bother Stan.
我來處理
I'll take care of it.
你認識一個認識羅路的人 對吧?
You know a guy that knew Rollo, right?
查查他在這附近有沒有家人 好嗎?
Find out if he had any family around here, will ya?
好的
All right.
克萊默小姐?
Miss Kramer?
-很抱歉打擾你  -羅路死了?
-I'm sorry to disturb you.  -Rollo's dead.
-是的  -被人殺了?
-Yes.  -Whacked?
是的 沒錯
As it were, yes.
是的
As it were.
好吧 謝謝你的提醒
Well, thanks for the heads up.
我會去查查他到底有沒有買
I'll make sure to look up that life insurance policy
人壽保險
he never got around to getting.
我來是想問個問題
I came here to discuss a problem that's arisen.
如果我對你的問題不感興趣呢?
And if I'm not interested in your problem?
哦 那麼…
Oh, well...
我明白了
I see.
你會用膠帶封住我的嘴
You'll slap duct tape over my mouth
然後把我塞進後備箱
and shove me in the trunk.
除非你對這個感興趣
Only if you're into that kind of thing.
只是想聊會
Just wanna talk.
車裡等我 甜甜圈
Wait in the car, Donut.
你剛剛殺了我的前夫 就不請你喝了
I'd offer you one, but you just killed my ex.
可你看起來並不傷心
You don't seem too upset.
就憑他做的那些勾當
I expected him to be deceased long before today,
我還以為他早就掛了
given the business he was in.
咦?
Huh.
你喜歡收集動物屍體 克萊默小姐?
You have a thing for dead animals, Miss Kramer?
我叫瑪茜 是個標本師
Marcie. I'm a taxidermist.
嗯 這樣的人不多
Mm. Don't find many of those.
很小眾
It's a niche thing.
他看起來很生氣
He looks angry.
就像有人偷了他的橡子 他要讓他們付出代價
Like someone stole his acorns and he's gonna make 'em pay.
真的嗎?
Really?
我不太懂海狸的表達方式
I'm not up on my beaver expressions.
-我可能說錯了  -我想表達它憤怒的情緒
-I could be wrong.  -I was going for indignant.
哦 是的 我明白了
Oh, yeah. I see it.
千萬別亂動我的橡子
Don't ever mess with my acorns.
我這裡有個小問題 呃…
I have a small problem, Miss, uh..
-瑪茜  -瑪茜
-Marcie.  -Marcie.
我必須向某人證明
I have to convince a certain person
外面後備箱裡的屍體確實是羅路
that the body in that trunk out there is indeed Rollo.
臉花了?
Something happen to his face?
對 臉沒了
Yeah. It's missing.
連同他頭部的其他部分
Along with the rest of his head.
如果你能陪我走一趟
There's five grand in it for you
證明羅路確實是羅路 就能拿五千塊
if you come with me and vouch that Rollo is indeed Rollo.
我需要錢
I could use the money.
但我發過誓不會再沾你們的圈子
But I swore I'd never get back into that world.
所以 我給你省點錢 也給自己省點時間
So, I'll save you the dough and myself some time.
我哥哥是個紋身師
Brother's a tattoo artist.
他給我和羅路紋了一對情侶紋身當作結婚禮物
Gave Rollo and I matching tattoos as a wedding gift.
-哦  -在我們的屁股上
-Oh.  -Our ass cheeks.
我去年把紋身洗了
I had Rollo removed last year.
你為什麼要這麼做?
Why'd you?
消除他的痕跡?
Have him removed?
我不知道
I don't know.
正常人都會吧
It's usually along the lines of someone
不然咋和其他人約會啊上床啊什麼的
trying to fuck someone else over, that type of thing.
對這檔子事兒羅路可是樂此不疲
That type of thing would be on the top of Rollo's resume.
是啊 明白了吧
Well, there you go now.
總之 他回到了比洛克希
Anyway, he.. He made it back here to Biloxi
而這恰好是我老闆的地盤
and it just happens to be my boss's territory.
所以 我們對新奧爾良的同事們很客氣
So, we're being courteous to our colleagues in New Orleans.
我喜歡你們的彬彬有禮
I love how you guys are so courteous.
打開後備箱 甜甜圈
Pop the trunk, Donut.
這窗簾真嚇人
Horrible drapes.
是啊 很襯那間廚房
Yeah, they went nice with the kitchen.
-這就是羅路的屁股  -看到沒? 來吧 夥計
-That's Rollo's ass.  -See? Come on, man.
我們不需要他的人頭了
We didn't need his head, after all.
你白生氣了
You got all pissy for nothing.
-你為什麼不…  -啊哦
-Why don't you...  -Oops.
你肯定不知道 拜加和羅路在安哥拉做過好監友
Bet you didn't know Beggars and Rollo were cellmates at Angola.
他肯定近距離看過那個紋身
Pretty sure he's seen that tattoo up close.
斯坦會不高興的 甜甜圈
Stan's not gonna like this, Donut.
-別叫我甜甜圈  -好吧
-Stop calling me Donut!  -Okay.
槍拿出來 槍
Get your gun out! Gun!
現在
Now.
扔車裡
Put it in the car.
去他的斯坦
Fuck Stan.
拜加說我可以隨時來為他工作
Beggar said I could come work for him anytime.
他勢頭正旺
He's moving up.
這個正好能當我的投名狀
And this'll prove I'm ready for his crew.
要是再聽到有人叫我甜甜圈
If I ever hear anybody call me Donut again,
我就回來活剮了你
I'm gonna come back and I'm gonna gut you.
老東西
Old timer.
別叫我甜甜圈 操你媽的
Don't call me Donut, motherfucker!
我想我還不知道你的名字
I don't believe I got your name.
查理
Charlie.
我要發達了 我要發達了
I'm moving up, baby! I'm moving up!
嗚！
Woo!
哦 噓
Ooh, sh..
哦 該死
Oh, shit.
你以前和他合作過嗎?
Have you worked with him before?
不 是第一次
No, first time.
-真是一團糟  -沒事 車是偷的
-What a mess.  -It's okay. The car is stolen.
我是說那小子 看起來射到了自己
I was referring to the kid. Looks like he shot himself.
嗯 他更擅長用刀
Well, he was more of a knife guy.
見鬼
Shit.
嗯…
Well...
你知道 他倆…
you know, they're kinda..
個頭差不多
Kinda the same size.
也許可以去找找你哥哥
Maybe go visit your brother,
他是紋身師 也許他可以… 你懂的
the tattoo artist, maybe he could, you know,
再紋一個 咋樣?
kinda.. No?
好吧 但我不會砍下他的頭
Fine, but I'm not cutting his head off.
瑪卡.羅爾著《前世繪》
"是的 斯科蒂.波特
Yeah, Scotty Porter
"在場上很活躍
looking a lot more active out there.
他進步得真快 這傢伙"
He's really coming along, that guy.
-你放了香菜?  -沒
-You put cilantro in here?  -No.
嗯 我明顯嘗到了檸檬的味道
Well, I distinctly taste lemon.
-對 這叫檸檬  -我討厭香菜
-Yeah. It's called lemon.  -I detest cilantro.
所以我用的檸檬
That's why I used lemon.
你 這雞肉是在多米尼克餐廳買的嗎?
Did you.. Did you get this chicken at that Domenic's?
多米尼克餐廳在北末廣場 比洛克希可沒有
Domenic's is in the North End. We're in Biloxi.
對啊 我腦子短路了估計
That's right, I don't know what the heck's gotten into me.
總之 重點是 它很好吃 別誤會我的意思
Anyway, the point is, it's very good, don't get me wrong.
即便是加香菜 也很好吃
It's very good, even with the cilantro.
我覺得 你該開一家餐館
I think personally that you should open a restaurant.
嗯 做這個行當得會偷工減料
Well, the only way to make money in that business is to skim.
你會偷工減料搞餐飲嗎
And you can't skim off yourself.
不 好吧 我的意思是 正常人誰會去
No, well, I mean, who in their right mind
搞餐飲?
goes into the restaurant business?
餐館生意錢不好賺
There's no money in.. In the restaurant business.
一點也不好
None whatsoever.
你知道 你可不能有
You know, you have to divest yourself
這種想法啊 查理
of that notion, Charlie.
-嗯  -咋了?
-Uh  -huh.  -What?
看比賽 斯坦
Watch the game, Stan.
斯坦.穆林 我的老闆
Stan Mullin, my boss.
他在比洛克希經營了47年
He's run Biloxi for 47 years.
他開始忘事已經有一段時間了
Been a while since he started forgetting things.
好的
Okay.
因此 我自告奮勇
So, I took it upon myself
來照顧他
to look out for him.
這是我欠他的
I owed him that.
我給你買了魚油
I got you some fish oils!
富含歐米茄3
Omega threes.
對心臟有好處
Good for your heart.
剩菜都在冰箱裡 餓了熱熱
Leftovers are in the fridge in case you're hungry later.
好的
Yeah.
-那孩子真可憐  -是啊 真遺憾
-Too bad about the kid.  -Yeah, it's a shame.
讓小孩子做正事
What were you thinking,
你是咋想的?
letting a young kid like that do a job like that?
對不起 斯坦
I'm sorry, Stan.
不會再有了
Won't let it happen again.
-會有麻煩嗎?  -不會
-We gonna have any trouble?  -No.
我已經處理好了
I took care of it.
-睡個好覺  -謝了 搭檔
-Sleep well.  -Thanks, partner.
拜加.麥卡多
Beggar Mercado,
從小流氓混成了九街區老大
street thug turned Ninth Ward crew chief.
{\